<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Projects on Rodrigo Lara</title>
    <link>https://rodrigolaram.github.io/Lara_Portfolio/post/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Projects on Rodrigo Lara</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 02 Mar 2017 12:00:00 -0500</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://rodrigolaram.github.io/Lara_Portfolio/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>[In Progress] Financial Portfolio App</title>
      <link>https://rodrigolaram.github.io/Lara_Portfolio/post/chapter-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rodrigolaram.github.io/Lara_Portfolio/post/chapter-3/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;m working on a app to keep track of all my financial investments from stocks to cryptos.
This project was started in December 2021.
  For full project click the following links
 &amp;ldquo;GitHub Repository&amp;rdquo;    </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Correlation between College Football teams stats and victories</title>
      <link>https://rodrigolaram.github.io/Lara_Portfolio/post/chapter-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rodrigolaram.github.io/Lara_Portfolio/post/chapter-2/</guid>
      <description>Methods:  Used different R programming libraries for data analysis; tidyverse, broom, infer. Read, cleaned, analyzed and plotted different data from numerous files. Constructed a model and hypothesised the final outcome of the investigation. Computed and tested the hypothesis and recorded final results.    Introduction.
College football is vastly popular across the United States, as it rakes in several millions of spectators every year. With the high-energy and competitiveness of college football (or perhaps college sports in general), there’s no doubt why it’s so popular, especially amongst the students.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Is NAFTA responsible for Mexico&#39;s obesity epidemic?</title>
      <link>https://rodrigolaram.github.io/Lara_Portfolio/post/chapter-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rodrigolaram.github.io/Lara_Portfolio/post/chapter-1/</guid>
      <description>Methods:  Used different Python libraries for data analysis; Pandas, Numpy, Statsmodels.api, Matplotlib.pyplot. Read, cleaned, analyzed and plotted different data from numerous files. Constructed a model and hypothesised the final outcome of the investigation. Computed and tested the hypothesis and recorded final results.    Introduction.
The North America Free Trade Agreement (NAFTA) was an agreement signed by Canada, Mexico, and the United States that created a trilateral trade block in North America.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
